

# **PLATFORMS**

#### in LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/svetosla v-yordanov003/

GitHub

https://github.com/yordanov03

Web Card

https://yordanov03.github.io/

#### **LANGUAGES**

**English** 

German ••••

# **SKILLS**

C# · SQL · Javascript · Typescript ·

HTML5 · CSS · Mongodb · .NetCore ·

ASP.NET · .NetFramework · Angular · Git ·

Azure · Docker · Kubernetes · CI/CD ·

 ${\sf Microservices} \cdot {\sf Bitbucket} \cdot {\sf Redux} \cdot {\sf Rxjs}$ 

#### **PROJECTS**

# Wohngeld Go

#### Link

 State projects aimed at providing financial aid for housing rentals

# **NOTABLE CERTIFICATION**

Azure Developer Associate

**Cloud Solutions Developer AZ-204** 

Azure Cosmos DB Developer

**Microsoft DP420 Certificate** 

**Azure Fundamentals** 

**Microsoft certified AZ-900** 

# REFERENCE LETTERS

Swisscom AG

Credit Suisse AG

thinfabrics Gmbh

Hewlett Packard Enterprise

DXC technology

# Svetoslav Yordanov

# MicrosoftDeveloper Associate

+4179 507 3951 @ svetoslav.yordanov.003@gmail.com

∇urich, Switzerland

#### SUMMARY

Passionate Software Engineer with several years of experience in developing web applications and backend systems. Skilled at writing clear, concise code that is easy to maintain and troubleshoot. Experienced in working with both small and large teams across multiple projects and companies. Able to work independently of remote locations or in office environments as needed by the company.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Full Stack Developer

2023 - Present

#### Swisscom AG

- Spearhead the development of scalable applications, delivering efficient solutions that enhance corporate security, network overview and business functionality.
- Design and implement Network Access Control (NAC) solutions, utilizing real-time state management tools to enhance system monitoring, security, and performance across diverse IT environments.
- Proactively manage potential security vulnerabilities through layered security protocols within the network infrastructure, ensuring top-tier security standards

# Full Stack Developer

2022 - 2022

#### Credit Suisse AG

- Creation of web tools with .NetCore, Angular and SQL of significant matter for the decision-making for future investments
- Proactively involved in the full lifecycle of tools for process automation
- Developing optimizations and cost-effectiveness via creating custom-tailored tools according to the needs of the business
- Cloud application development and migration

# Full Stack Developer

2021 - 2022

#### Freelancer

- Design, implementation and deployment of tools as per customer specifications
- Monolith or microservices architecture based in cloud environment
- Integration of third party applications (Dynatrace, Keypay, Mailchimp etc.)
- Performing root cause analysis to identify bugs and roll out fixes to production

# Software Developer

2020 - 2021

2013 - 2015

#### thinfabrics Gmbh - Bulpros consulting

- Lead Developer, participating actively decision-making concerning tech stack and deployment
- Developing new features and integration with existing services for state project, aimed at providing financial aid for housing commodities
- Refactor legacy code and update internal customer framework
- Due to timely project completion, the development of 7 more projects was entrusted to us by the same costumer

#### **EDUCATION**

# Web developer 2017 - 2019 Software university

communications

University of National and World Economy

Master's degree in Marketing and

Bachelor in International Relations 2008 - 2012

University of National and World Economy